sisters this is E on ey censored
Supernatural Bible changes on YouTube
and today is the 12th of June
2024 wanted to let you know that my
latest book armies of the aliens was
released this morning on Amazon and this
particular book covers all the words
what all of them but several verses in
Scripture that have new words in it
related to the Alien Invasion could be
extra terrestrial language or also
illegal alien invasion because we are
seeing our nation here in the United
States and other Western nations are
being inundated right now with illegal
aliens by
Design the Bible is being supernaturally
changed and the changes are prolific and
obvious on every single page there is an
agenda to what they're doing to bring in
the reign of the
Antichrist and we are seeing right now a
great falling away because the verses
are perverted and there's blasphemy all
through scripture
today now we know that Jesus is the
Christ the son of God king of kings and
Lord of lords and he is the word of God
according to John 1:1 and Revelations
1913 no matter what these evil doers do
to our Bibles they cannot erase the word
of God because the word of God endures
forever but our bibles are definitely
changing and I've been researching this
for over seven and a half years there's
no doubt in my mind now in this
particular book what I want to show you
are certain verses I've included over
maybe I don't know 170
verses that are included in this little
book that include language that would
fall into the category of Alien Invasion
and I'll show you a few of them so first
let me just show you that this is
available on Amazon this is the web page
and I give you a description of what
we're seeing so for example and I've
included in the description on
Amazon we now have words related to both
types of aliens illegal aliens as well
as
extraterrestrials and various
professions that are involved with
aliens so for example we have armies of
aliens officers deputies space Gra
lawyers outer Darkness Forum think of
world economic Forum right and then we
have even the tribe of the
Nephilim that's right one of the 12
tribes of Israel nefeli has been chained
to the tribe of the Nephilim complete
mockery but thereover as I mentioned
I've categorized or identified 170
verses with language that relates to the
AL Al
Invasion and let me go ahead and show
you a few of those uh right here so
here's one Isaiah 45:17 so just so you
know that on every single page is one
verse and it makes it really easy just
to open it up and research for yourself
and even have a conversation with
somebody about what they're reading and
talk to them about these
agendas because there are several of
them that are being
infiltrated into scripture to prepare
the way for the reign of the Antichrist
so here's this verse Isaiah
457 but Israel shall be saved in the
Lord with an everlasting salvation ye
shall not be ashamed nor confounded
World Without End this verse is a total
rewrite never read it before the change
of the scripture first of all there is a
World Without End so this is a lie
because we we know for a fact that this
present Earth and Heavens will be burnt
up like a squrrel and we learned that in
the New
Testament and don't say it has to do
with people because people will perish
in their sins without repentance and
forgiveness of
sins and I just don't recognize this and
also it doesn't even make
sense so that's one verse another one is
this one this is second p 210 and I've
included it because the word government
was plopped in here and listen to what
it says today and has other new words do
but chiefly them that walk after the
Flesh in the lust of uncleanness and
despise
government presumptuous are they
self-willed they are not afraid to speak
evil of
dignities do you know what this is about
this is about preparing the church not
to speak out against the corruption the
wickedness that's happening in
government as if it were a sin to call
out such wickedness that we're seeing
and have experienced through the
government so we also know the
government is complicit in the illegal
alien invasion and potentially these
extraterrestrial invasions that we're
seeing using technology that we don't
know
yet the little
people are they using Project Blue beam
perhaps are they the Nephilim
perhaps what is going on let me go ahead
and show you another one this is uh Mark
4:13 and it's mentioning the Nephilim
well Nephilim was used one time in the
Book of
Genesis and now that's been erased in
the King James Bible replaced with the
word
Giants but now we have the 12 tribes of
um Israel we have one of them changed
from Nephi to
Nephilim and so this word this verse has
the land of the Nephilim here how crazy
is that that's Mark
4:13 another one is Titus 3:13 talking
about lawyers zenis the lawyer have you
ever heard of him or her bring zenis the
lawyer and Apollos on their Journey
diligently that nothing be wanting unto
them them it's a total rewrite lawyers
were never in scripture before let alone
zenis and this verse doesn't even make
sense another one I'll read to you is
this one Ezekiel 7:23 with the illegal
aliens that are crossing our border we
are seeing a rise in crime across
Western Nations that are being
invaded this is what the verse says
today in Ezekiel make a chain for the
land is full of bloody crime
and the city is full of violence well
are we not seeing that happen
today
absolutely so this is just a preview of
some of the verses I show in this little
book I begin with an introduction as to
what's happening and scripture verses
about the changes of scripture how the
Bible warned us I also Identify some of
the words that the reader could look for
as they're reading through the scripture
verses and also Al to note some of the
mistakes or errors that we now see in
scripture inclusive of emoticons grammar
errors punctuation errors new people
words erased uh doctrinal errors and so
forth and then I also share um how
someone can become born again very
important to share that and then I also
share a little bit about the book and
about the supernatural Bible changes
these events that we're seeing happen
today these lyes signs and
wonders so with that said I hope this
book will be a great resource for you um
I have other ones that I'll be
publishing soon all of these are
created with the strong desire that
these tools will be useful for you and
helpful to anyone who's seeking the
truth about what's happening to the
Bible so be strong and courageous
brothers and sisters do not fear or be
dismayed for the Lord your God is with
you wherever you go until next time